{
    "id": "171e6d65252244f9969487dd542fe163",
    "title": "Phrasal Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "She ……………….. her mother.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "takes after",
                "takes on",
                "takes away"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "76fbff4825b845b3abec88fb7fafea7e"
        },
        {
            "question": "The militants took the captives ………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "away",
                "after"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "74f9242151074040aa24ab289da026b8"
        },
        {
            "question": "The opposition leader insisted that the minister should ………………… his remarks.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "take after",
                "take back",
                "take down"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "32f0d8e0967d4630909015ea49363c8b"
        },
        {
            "question": "Please ....................... what I say.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "take down",
                "take off",
                "take out"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "42b6a681253f4c4d8b887d2d51a95d96"
        },
        {
            "question": "Activists forced the shop to ………………….. their neon sign.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "take off",
                "take down",
                "take back"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7a0f0a0d57e048e6a1407ba580a31080"
        },
        {
            "question": "You can’t take him ………………. an idiot.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "after",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e2ae468bcc2b4c1f90cdf91a47e72bc2"
        },
        {
            "question": "We were ....................... by a con artist.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "taken out",
                "taken in",
                "taken for"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3edadd07169343ca8ec5f00ba73e4719"
        },
        {
            "question": "Hindus take their shoes ………………… before entering a house.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "off",
                "on",
                "out"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "34ce2a699448473ea12741b98ec9550c"
        },
        {
            "question": "As I was not feeling well, I decided to take a day …………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "away",
                "off",
                "down"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3ae99c00fa2c460fbace0992045d7139"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am afraid you have ..................... too much responsibility.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "taken out",
                "taken on",
                "taken off"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a9479bddbde948528efd0e8eb38ec407"
        }
    ]
}